{
    "subject": "resource/Yul_Brynner",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Russian_male_film_actors",
    "human_readable": "Yul Brynner is a subject of the category Russian male film actors.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8799422383308411,
            "question": "Is Yul Brynner male?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8757650256156921,
            "question": "Name some famous films starring Yul Brynner."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8266029953956604,
            "question": "What kind of actor is Yul Brynner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901875972747803,
            "question": "In what category is Yul Brynner classified?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6811073422431946,
            "question": "What is Yul Brynner known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6226403713226318,
            "question": "What is Yul Brynner's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5666797161102295,
            "question": "What nationality is Yul Brynner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3683641850948334,
            "question": "What era was Yul Brynner most active in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34460145235061646,
            "question": "What are some awards or recognition Yul Brynner received?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.289193332195282,
            "question": "Did Yul Brynner have any notable physical characteristics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Yul Brynner is a subject of the category Russian male film actors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7874_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some awards or recognition Yul Brynner received?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7874_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What era was Yul Brynner most active in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7874_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Yul Brynner?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7874_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7874_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents mention Yul Brynner as a Russian-born actor, and also describe him playing various roles on stage and screen. This suggests that he would fall under the category of Russian male film actors."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Yul Brynner, including his nationality as Russian-born and his status as an actor in both stage and film. This supports the categorization of Yul Brynner as a subject under the category \"Russian male film actors.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}